LARRY LACONI

705 Quinnipiac Avenue, New Haven, Connecticut 06513 • cell: 203-927-0818 soverylarry@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY and OBJECTIVE

Upcoming University of Connecticut Coding Bootcamp Graduate (Sept 2020) seeks position in software development, test or deployment. Enthusiastic professional with multitude of experiences with client facing positions.

UConn Coding Bootcamp -

Apr 2020 - Sept 2020

22 week Full Stack software course focused on: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, Database Theory, MongoDB, MySQL, Command Line, Git, Java, and more. Portfolio URL:

SKILLS

- Superior interpersonal skills: Negotiator, Team-player, Conflict Resolver, Closer.
- Curious and forward-thinking with a passion for new technologies.
- Creative problem solving and managerial skills.
- Proven experience with Major Corporate Clients, University and Government entities.

RELEVANT WORK HISTORY

Commuter Program Manager

Oct 2017 to Jan 2020

CTRIDES/AECOM - ROCKY HILL, CONNECTICUT

- Assist medium to large municipalities, businesses, Higher Ed and non-profits to reduce employee single vehicle miles traveled within the state of Connecticut.
- Working on behalf of CT-DOT to disseminate information on commuter options and further state transportation goals.
- Conduct employer onsite outreach events for employees to learn about CTrides assistance and resources.
- Created new 'Bike at Lunch' event to promote Bike New Haven & CTrides concurrently.
- Assisting in rollout of Micro-Transit project with 9Town Transit.

Government Partnership Executive
Partner Development Representative
SEECLICKFIX - NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT

Nov 2015 to July 2017 Jan 2015 to Nov 2015

- Negotiated Contracts for software as a service (SAAS) with municipalities.
- Closed Qualified Leads led to \$140,000 in new annual recurring revenue.
- Qualified Leads led to \$110,000 in annual recurring revenue.
- Assisted in Training new hires in sales support roles.
- Pioneered Partner Development Rep role for SeeClickFix.

.

National Accounts Manager

Sept 2005 to Dec 2014

YALE UNIVERSITY PRESS - NEW HAVEN, CONNECTICUT

- Managed sales to large wholesalers and specialty markets. Account responsibilities produced \$8 million+ in annual sales.
- Managed premium and bulk sales to corporate clients (e.g. Urban Outfitters, Crate and Barrel) and organizations including Conde Nast, W.K. Kellogg Foundation and other internationally focused non-profits. Largest sale netted \$330,000 to the Press.
- Responsible for sales presentations, marketing programs, sales goals, title selection, and marketing co-op for all territory customers.
- Prioritized daily workflows, including all inbound calls, quotes and sales-related inquiries.
- Actively collaborated with editorial, marketing and finance departments.

National Accounts Sales Rep

June 2000 to Aug 2005

GLOBE PEQUOT AND LYONS PRESS - GUILFORD, CONNECTICUT AND NEW YORK, NEW YORK

- Managed buyer relations, marketing and seasonal sales calls to national accounts.
- Supervised and trained two sales coordinators.
- Developed prospective titles.

Processing Supervisor and Trade Buyer

June 1995 to May 2000

BAKER AND TAYLOR – BRIDGEWATER, NEW JERSEY

- Managed 15 employees responsible for library book conversion process. Conducted employee reviews and daily staffing needs.
- Responsible for front list buys, backlist replenishment and successful business relations for 30 major trade publishers.
- Arranged and executed "Publisher New Book Showcase": coordinated top 50
 national publishers in presenting seasonal highlights for staff and regional
 acquisitions librarians.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Management Penn State University - Erie, Pennsylvania

Larry Laconi References

Karen Jenkins Founder & Board Member New Haven Coalition for Active Transportation kjenkins@development4good.com 732-325-4003

Lee Cruz
Director of Community Outreach
The Community Foundation of Greater New Haven
lcruz@cfgnh.org
203-668-7074

Tom Girard
Director of Retail Operations
Zane's Cycles
tg@zanes.com
203-868-9585